<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Richie my bb >3</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "I know most girlfriends write their lovers cute \nletters and shit but I decided to make you an app
        because that's just how I roll fam :P\n\n"

        "I want you to know that I think of you everyday and that I do care about you a lot. "
        "I know I don't say it often enough or message you constantly or send you lots of funny"
        "memes BUT you have to believe me when I proclaim that I am madly in love with you\n\n"
        ":) And may the scrolling begin" \n\n

        "Bb I want you to know that I really appreciate all the little things you do to make me happy. \n"
        "I secretly love it when you compliment me and I love the way you make me feel like I'm really"
        "funny and smart and pretty even though I know I'm just a coco potato.\n"

        "I really loved the fact that you flew up to visit me after your gonggong's passing just"
        "so we could spend quality time together."
        "We both know we should have been productive that weekend but at least it was fun :P \n\n"

        "Thank you for always letting me pick the food we eat and almost all the activities that we"
        "do. I'm grateful that you're a simple man who just enjoys frolicking around with me."
        "Whether its a sunset hike, hackathon, TedTalk or just chilling at the beach, you have been"
        "my favorite ADVENTURE BUDDY!!!\n"
        "Thank you for keeping me warm. I get tingles every time I feel your skin against my skin"
        "and when I can smell the distinctive swagger.\n\n"
        "PS it smells different on you versus when other people wear it.\n\n"

        "I love you more than sexy times but I will admit, once you gave me sexy times, my body "
        "craved more and more of Richie."
        "Night after night, morning after morning, HOUR AFTER HOUR, you continue to blow my mind in"
        "such ways that all our neighbors probably hate us ;)"
        "\nSince we are both still kids in our twenties, lets keep the party going until you're soft and I'm dry :P\n"
        "
        >3
        \n"
        "Now to pop the question *grabs whatever courage I have left* \n"
        "\n
        Dear Richie,
        Will you accept my awkward but enduring love and be my boyfriend? Do you promise to not hurt"
        "me and to love me even though I can be a spontaneous hot mess?\n"
        "If so, then this is the point where we can hug and I can enjoy this moment where we are in each other's arms."
        "\n I secretly hope that you agree to keep our anniversary date as
        JUNE 24, 2017__06/24/2016
        rather than have me remember whatever day I decided to show you this app >3 \n\n"

        "Even if you reject my love, I want you to know that I wish you the best in life and I hope"
        "you find happiness in whatever you choose to pursue and with whomever you decide to share your"
        "affections with. I know you will do great things and frankly, you don't need me to achieve them.\n\n"

        "But hopefully I can look forward to a future with many more adventures WITH YOU :D\n"
        "You can be the french fries to my tater tot, and together we will taste fabulous dipped in matcha ice cream\n"
        "Thank you for your patience and I hope your day was as amazing as you :)\n\n"

        "With lots of love,
        (haha like more than a jar of pickles)\n\n"
        "Colleen Lau, cocoa tater tots
        >3\n"
        <!--
            things I like that he did/does
            funny inside jokes
            future
            ask the question
        -->

    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Pics</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Cute Things</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">Important</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Are you Richie Chio?</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">A cute checklist of all the things that
        makes Richie the great bb that he is >3
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Yo name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">Richie Chio</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Talk to me fam</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Never</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Always</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entries">
        <item>Entry 1</item>
        <item>Entry 2</item>
        <item>Entry 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entry_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value" />

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications - talk to Coco </string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling2">Scroll me more</string>
</resources>
